Please subscribe to our channel!
Thank you for watching!
I'm a little blind.
Elephant.
This is not important.
This is important.
Oh, okay, okay.
Even Venus wrapped in dumpling skin on the show.
Don't look at your face.
Venus.
Look at me.
There's an elephant.
I went to Utsunomiya to eat gyoza.
Today I'll be the one with the camera, and it'll show me doing what I do.
I'm eating Utsunomiya gyoza.
That's good.
You're from Utsunomiya, right?
You're from Tochigi, right?
Yay!
Here it is, today's big hit!
Chinjaeru!
Delicious!
Grilled dumplings!
Bon appétit!
Let's start with the baked dumplings.
I have to have them in my mouth.
Bon appétit.
Just like that?
What? What's it like?
Why don't you write a report on your book?You're an author, you're a reporter.
Yeah, these dumplings have a mellow sweetness.
What do you mean?
It's cool that you guys eat so much.
I don't think so.
You don't have any of that shoujo manga stuff.
Me?
What kind of tics?
Shonen Jump.
Shonen Jump?
Me? Like, this kind of stand up thing?
Something like that?
But you're not the hero?
I don't feel like a hero.
I know exactly what you mean.
Now that you've done a play, don't you want to do a movie?
Yes, for sure.
I'm going to do a coming-of-age movie.
And a music video,
Music videos have a very adolescent feel to them these days.
Sure, the next stage...
If not a stage, then a movie.
Happy!
A long time ago...
There's a movie with Ryubi Miyase.
There's a movie called Natsuyozora
It was a long time ago.
It's a short film
It's a short film about spring, summer, fall and winter.
They all had different layouts.So they were all different layouts.
That's four in one.
It's like a movie.
Don't you want to do that?
It was delicious.
Yes, I'm about to make my first appearance on a show in Tochigi Prefecture.
One of the best things about Tochigi is the gyoza (Chinese dumplings), which I have just eaten.
The taste of gyoza varies from restaurant to restaurant.
Gyoza tastes different in each restaurant, but they are very tasty everywhere you go.
So, if you come to Tochigi for an event, please try gyoza.
Well, yes...
After that, please go to Ashikaga.
Ashikaga Flower Park.
There is a very famous illumination.
We'll take you there for sightseeing.
There's also Ashikaga School, the oldest school in Japan.
You can also go to Nikko.
Or you can go to Nikko, which is in a different direction.
There are temples and so on.
There's so much nature, and I want to eat good food.
I want nature.
If you want to take in the natural air...
please come to Tochigi.
Yes! Tochigi for me is
Tochigi is like my hometown
It's like my hometown.
I mean, it's like a hometown.
Well, it's like a second hometown.
I was born in Miyagi.I was born in Miyagi Prefecture.
I was born in Miyagi, but Tochigi is an essential part of my life.
Tochigi is an indispensable part of my life.
Tochigi is a rival of Miyagi.
It's like Miyagi vs Tochigi, one against the other.
Beef tongue versus strawberries.
I have strong feelings for Tochigi.
Tochigi is my answer school.
Tochigi is my answer school, so it's like the "Anzai Sky".
When I take the Shinkansen back home.
I always go through there.
Utsunomiya never stops.
Just passing through.
Utsunomiya is right.
We're passing through.
It's over Tochigi, so it's come ashore many times.
It hasn't made landfall.
It's just passing through.
Today I understand the charm of Tochigi.
I'm sure...
It went up like a hammer.
Until I get nervous.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
After you've said hello...
Can I throw in a little something?
Please do.
I look forward to working with you.I look forward to working with you.
Please do me a favor.
Today, we are going to talk about a live concert that will be held
I'd like to talk about the live concert that will be held at the end of the year.
Ms. Nagai.
Ms. Nagai, please introduce yourself.
On Saturday, December 9th.
It will be held at Curly's Tochigi in Miyoshi.
Tochigi Prefecture's 150th anniversary
Commemorative event Tochigi Future Department
We would like to introduce you to Tochigi, a great place!
So, I would like to introduce
Artists who will perform on the day
We have invited them to our studio!
From One Love One Heart
Here are two of them!
We are One Love One Heart
Thank you very much for coming.
Thank you for coming. Please give my best regards to you.
We are a group of nine members, both male and female, and we understand that you have a lot of people in your group.
Our goal is to be a comprehensive entertainment group that not only sings and dances, but also challenges every kind of challenge, including theatrical performances.
The show is over. Were you nervous?
Not at all.
The MC, Mr. Nagai, had a great ability to talk, and we didn't do anything at all.
We didn't do anything at all. We just talked. But he helped us a lot.
I learned a lot.
Thank you very much. It was a very good experience.
Ladies and gentlemen, this is Dotigi TV.
Yes, I'm Dotigi TV.Yes, I am here.
Thank you for your help here today.
Yes, I am very happy to be here today. It was a very good experience.
Today's VLOG was sightseeing in Tochigi.
It was sightseeing and work.
Yes. How was it?
How was it? What do you like about Tochigi?
Yes, I think so. As rivals in Meijo Prefecture, we would like to continue to improve each other.
We are going to improve each other.
How was it?
Yes, it was good. We all enjoyed the dumplings.
Next time, we will come back in winter to eat strawberries.
Yes, I see.
Oh, yeah.
Yay.
I heard they're coming.
Yes, they are. That's all for today.
Yeah.
Tighten it up somehow. Okay, then.
Well then, everyone, come to Tochigi.
protests